[Genius Girlfriend]
[Episode 23]
Get some sleep after drinking this.
What about you?
You haven't been back for days.
I'll help tidy up your place a bit.
[Quantum Entanglement]
[Parallel Universes]
Hello?
Can't find something?
I can come over right away. I'm...
You're amazing.
My draft paper for calculating
plasma turbulence,
the one with the diagram
drawn in green pen on the back,
you actually put it
with last week's
differential geometry notes.
Your idea was spot on.
Also, how did you think of putting
Turing's biography and
Fermat's Last Theorem together?
Your logic is so clear.
It's much easier to find
than when I put them away myself.
I'll never have to worry about
losing things again.
I...
Jiang Yubai,
I think you're a genius at organizing.
Gosh,
this talent of yours
is so worth developing.
I just put them there randomly.
As long as it's convenient for you.
It is, very convenient.
Are you home?
I...
Yes, I'm home.
Good.
Thank you.
Good night.
Duan.
Agent Tang, you're finally here.
It's really hard to get
a meeting with you.
Your favorites,
I ordered them all for you.
Go ahead and eat.
Mr. Duan, you're really spending today.
Isn't
this very normal?
Why do I feel like
you're not here to eat,
but to vent?
Spit it out. What is it?
What do I have to rant about?
My mood
is as beautiful as the weather today.
I just suddenly wanted to have
a few drinks with you.
Come on.
All right.
Whoever stops drinking first
today is a coward.
That's the Tang I know.
Come on.
Wait.
What?
Get in the frame.
Okay.
Do I look handsome?
Yes.
[Photos and Videos]
[Tang]
[Post]
Thank you, Mr. Duan, for the great treat.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
Bottoms up.
You really are a tough guy.
No warm-up at all.
I'll join you.
Let's eat.
What is it? Tell me.
Why can't I just have
some good food and drinks with you
to strengthen
our revolutionary friendship?
Oh, come on.
You've been in business for so long.
Surely you've made new friends.
You look like you're drinking your
sorrows away in dreary weather.
No.
I just knew you were craving hotpot,
so I found a good restaurant
to share with you.
Wait a minute.
Hello, Su Mo.
What's wrong? Aren't you at an audition?
Tingting, it was supposed to be my turn,
but Mr. Yang brought
a few more people over.
The casting director told me to wait here.
It's been quite a while.
What should I do?
What happened?
Didn't you ask the people there?
I asked.
But they didn't give me a clear answer.
Should I wait here
or go in and ask?
I'm coming over now.
Leave it to me.
Sorry, Duan.
I have an emergency and need to go.
It's your Su Mo again, isn't it?
Why is he acting like a three-year-old
and coming to you for everything?
No.
He's at an audition,
and they're keeping him waiting
for a long time.
Where's your professionalism?
He's asking others for a favor,
so waiting is to be expected.
If he can't even stand this
and calls for backup to play the victim,
wouldn't that just make them
dislike him more?
It's not easy for him
to get an opportunity.
We can't just hand it over
to someone else.
Besides, this is my job.
I have to deal with it.
That is what you call professionalism.
I'm leaving.
I'm confiscating
these two bottles of liquor
so you don't drink yourself into a stupor.
Fine.
Tang Tingting, you are really something.
I've handled it.
We should drink our liquor together.
Fill it up.
You're here.
I came to see you,
and to bring you a toy.
A binary star system model?
Did you make it?
It's so beautiful.
Do you like it?
It must have a lot of mechanisms.
You put the emerald here?
It's so pretty.
It looks like an emerald.
Any stone in your hands
would become a gem.
It must've been polished over time
to have such a perfect shape.
For you.
Why give it to me?
Because I want to.
It's so beautiful.
It's like the center
of a binary star system.
Why don't you take a break
from studying this?
You can do it another day.
Um...
You haven't tasted my cooking yet, right?
I've had the vegetables you prepared.
That's perfect.
I must show you my skills.
So...
How about radish and beef brisket stew?
You can also think about
what you want to eat for the week ahead.
No need to go through all that trouble.
Cooking takes a long time.
We can just order takeout.
Takeout isn't as hygienic
as home-cooked food.
Let me do it.
Then what should I do?
Just find something to do.
I'll go buy groceries first.
What's up? Hungry?
No.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Does it still hurt?
Your leg isn't healed yet.
Don't wander around.
Go back and sit down.
Wait for me a bit longer.
It'll be ready soon.
Why did you put the vegetables in
after turning off the heat?
Well, you have to
let it simmer
with the heat off for a while.
This is my secret recipe.
It tastes good only when
simmered this way.
What's wrong?
I'm hungry.
Hungry?
It's almost done.
Let's eat.
Food is ready.
It smells so good.
It looks delicious.
And it's my first time seeing two kinds
of radishes in this dish.
One is white radish,
and the other is carrot...
shreds.
That's my secret recipe.
Try it.
I know.
You must have done it on purpose.
I saw you turn the heat down
really low just now.
You definitely wanted me to taste it
when I'm the hungriest
to enjoy your secret recipe.
That's right.
You have to turn off the heat and
let it simmer
to make it taste good.
Is it good?
It's so delicious.
I'll try the beef.
It's been stewed until it's so tender.
That puzzle of yours
is quite difficult, isn't it?
It is quite hard.
Why don't you help me with it
after we finish eating?
Okay.
So good.
You must be sleepy.
No, I'm not.
Then
I'll head back first.
Thank you for today.
You stayed so late cooking for me.
It's nothing.
How are you getting back?
It's so late.
The buses have probably stopped running.
I'll just take a taxi.
That's too expensive.
I mean,
why don't you stay here tonight?
That wouldn't be appropriate.
Your brother will scold me again
if he finds out.
Just don't let him know.
I'm mainly worried it's unsafe
for you to go home alone.
I'll get you a blanket so you can
sleep on the floor here. How about that?
[Hematology Department]
Zeqiu, what brings you here?
I came to process Lin Zhixia's discharge
and have a chat with you.
You could've just called me to do it.
There was no need to make a special trip.
Her hospitalization
has already troubled you a lot.
I won't bother you
with something so trivial.
Don't be a stranger.
We are all friends.
How is Zhixia recovering?
Pretty well. She's recovering nicely.
Her leg still needs rest.
Don't rush to walk.
Avoid secondary injury.
I'll remind her later.
You've been working hard too.
You had to work
and take care of a patient.
It's not hard.
I've just been a bit busy lately.
At the hospital, I have your help.
As for Lin Zhixia,
she has Jiang Yubai taking care of her.
How are the two PhDs
I found for Zhixia last time?
If they're no good,
I can ask my mom to find someone else.
I understand what you mean.
But above all,
Lin Zhixia said she doesn't need them.
She can handle it herself.
Doesn't she lack manpower and resources?
These two people
should be of great help.
That's what I thought too.
I asked both you
and Jiang Yubai about this.
I thought your method
was more effective
and reliable.
But maybe Jiang Yubai
understands Lin Zhixia better.
What did he say?
He said Lin Zhixia doesn't need help,
and she can do it on her own.
I don't get it at all.
Get back to work. I'm leaving.
Of course it exists.
The core parameters of the Drake equation
mostly rely on subjective estimation.
Even if we take relatively
conservative values ​​
for these parameters,
some calculation results still indicate
that there are
thousands of extraterrestrial
civilizations in the Milky Way.
Equations are equations,
and evidence is evidence.
If there are so many
extraterrestrial civilizations,
where are they?
We haven't even found solid evidence
of a single alien bacterium yet.
Maybe the technological gap is too huge,
just like how ants can't understand
human radio waves,
Alternatively, their life forms
may be completely different
and unidentifiable to us.
Or maybe the Great Silence
itself is a signal.
An unprovable conjecture
is science fiction,
not science.
The spirit of science lies in
exploring the unknown.
Project Ozma,
a "Search for
Extraterrestrial Intelligence" project,
is exactly using scientific methods
to find evidence.
You can't assert that they don't exist
just because we haven't found them yet.
Okay.
Okay, I lose.
It's mainly because I also
truly believe that aliens exist.
Alas, I drew the opposition.
Giving up already?
Let's play a little longer.
The winner is decided.
I'm going to sleep.
Let's play a little longer.
Play with me a little longer.
It's time to sleep.
Jiang Yubai.
Jiang Yubai!
Jiang Yubai, wake up.
Jiang Yubai,
stop pretending to be asleep.
Jiang Yubai, wake up.
Wake up...
Are you hurt?
No.
Let me help you up.
I'll...
Have some water.
Dr. Shen.
What's with the brooding
handsome guy act here?
Why are you here?
It's too stuffy inside.
Look at you.
You look more like a patient
than those of us undergoing chemo.
Could it be...
A breakup?
Not exactly.
It's just...
A friend of mine.
He likes a girl,
but she seems to
already have feelings for someone else.
He's wondering
if he should let go.
You healthy people
really have nothing better to do.
Here I am,
wondering every day how to survive
the next treatment cycle
and whether I'll live to see tomorrow.
As for you,
you are perfectly fine
and have plenty of time.
You can love many people,
eat many meals,
and make many friends.
Just because someone doesn't like you,
you're moping around here.
What do you have to be unhappy about?
What you have is something
we wouldn't even dare to dream of.
Besides,
even if you can't be lovers,
you can still be friends or family.
There's no need to act like
it's the end of the world.
Get over it soon, Dr. Shen.
Don't waste your energy.
I'm still counting on you
to treat me in high spirits.
[Class Break]
Everyone.
Are you guys free this weekend evening?
It's been a long time
since our last gathering.
My treat.
Let's hang out.
Am I seeing things?
Dr. Shen is actually
organizing a gathering?
What a rare sight.
Plus one. The sun is rising from the west.
Did something trigger you, Dr. Shen?
Shen Fuxuan,
are you finally done with work?
Yes.
Bad timing, bro.
I have to oversee an offline promotion
this weekend.
I can't get away.
One of my artists has a sudden
schedule... I'm so miserable.
I'm free.
But...
I can't go out with my injury.
Me too. I still have
a few orders to finish.
It's okay. Let's meet next time.
Wait.
We might be absent,
but the drinks shouldn't be.
Since you asked,
we can't just let it go.
Let's hang out online right now.
Your treat. Have food and drinks delivered
to everyone.
We'll drink together on a video call!
I don't mind.
I agree. Dr. Shen's treat.
Thank you, Dr. Shen.
By the way, order
strawberry milk for Lin Zhixia.
You don't need to remind me.
Alright, online hangout it is.
Send me what you want to eat,
and I'll order for us.
[Cold beer, BBQ, beef, mutton]
[Grilled shrimp, grilled squid,
grilled vegetables]
[Plum wine, fried chicken,
fries, tteokbokki]
[Soda, BBQ, beef, mutton]
[Grilled shrimp, grilled squid,
potato slices, grilled vegetables]
[No. 1092, Dongyue East Road,
Binjiang District]
[Fun Biking Co., Ltd.]
[No. 1080, Wenrui Road, Jiang District]
[Star Shine Media Co., Ltd.]
[Strawberry milk, chips,
cookies, prawn crackers]
[Recipient: Tang Tingting]
[Address: No. 1080 Wenrui Road,
Jiang District, Huacheng City]
[Star Shine Media Co., Ltd.]
Eight bottles.
[Recipient: Lin Zhixia]
[Address: Binjiang District,
Huacheng City]
[Room 503, Building 2, Qingbei University]
Strawberry milk.
Everyone is here.
Long time no see.
Let me say a few words first.
Here,
let us first celebrate
the success of Mr. Shen's
first-ever hangout organization.
Although this method is a bit cyberpunk,
it doesn't matter.
Come on, let's make a toast, shall we?
Cheers.
-Cheers!
Shen Fuxuan,
let me toast you individually.
Thank you, Dr. Shen,
for taking care of me
during my hospitalization.
Cheers.
But I can only drink milk.
You don't have to drink the whole glass.
Dr. Shen, you're such a good drinker.
Zhixia really has some pull.
Don't let me drink alone.
Let's all toast together.
We shouldn't just drink.
Let's play a game.
Does Mr. Duan have any brilliant ideas?
You guys play. I'll just watch.
Come on, let's play...
Fifteen Twenty.
The two of us can start first.
Bring it on. I'll bet 100 cups.
Come on.
15, 20, 10.
15, 20, 15.
Drink.
Hurry up and drink now.
-15, 20, 10.
-15, 20, 15.
-15, 20, 20.
-15, 20, 5.
Drink up.
You've got some skills.
15, 20, 5.
15, 20, 10.
You lost again.
Bottoms up.
Rock, paper, scissors.
It's okay.
Go, Jiang.
Again.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
You are no good either. Drink.
Jiang is no good.
Zhixia, it's all up to you.
I only know how to play
rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors is fine.
Rock, paper, scissors.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
Beautiful.
I lost.
Zhixia, it has to be you.
Bottoms up for me.
Duan Qiyan, are you drunk?
Hello, Zhou.
Shen Fuxuan,
regarding the matter
you asked me to look into,
there is some progress.
Our college does have a cutting-edge
gene-editing research project
on blood disorders.
Recently,
it just received ethical approval.
They are searching globally
for rare cases with high compatibility.
The case you sent me a while ago
is quite a good match.
Really?
But I have to be upfront.
This treatment is too new,
and the risk is extremely high.
The current estimated survival rate
is only about 10 to 20 percent.
Frankly speaking, it's a huge gamble.
10 to 20 percent?
Yes, and that's the best-case scenario.
Dr. Shen,
Shui's preliminary evaluation
results are out.
Things are not looking great.
The bone marrow aspiration results show
that her response
to the first-line intensive regimen
is very poor.
The tumor burden
didn't decrease as expected,
and some indicators even went up.
The director just reviewed it.
He said that
in the short term,
we're out of effective standard treatment
options.
Zhou,
please send all relevant materials,
detailed project data, potential risks,
and all data on the success rates,
to me in the most detailed
and unvarnished version.
I will evaluate them carefully.
Okay.
Hello?
Listen to me first.
It's an emergency.
My parents are making a surprise visit.
They said they're almost downstairs
and will be coming up soon.
Don't panic.
I'll be right back.
Help me ask for leave.
Sure thing.
Dad, Mom.
This is Lin Zeqiu.
Hello, Sir and Ma'am.
Come in and have a seat.
Dad, you...
Mom, that's the bedroom over there.
Would you like some water, Sir?
Sir,
Ma'am,
please have a glass of water.
What is the relationship
between you two now?
Sir, we...
This is my boyfriend.
We live together now.
Jin Baihui.
How can you say that?
Is this the result
of your years of studying
and education?
Let's go. We'll talk at home.
I'm not leaving.
Hurry up and let's go.
We'll talk when we get back.
If you have something to say, say it here.
I don't want to scold you
in front of an outsider.
Lin Zeqiu is not an outsider.
You can say whatever you want.
You think you're all grown up now?
My words don't mean anything
to you anymore?
Fine.
Then let me ask you this.
You just moved in with him
without a proper status?
Where is your upbringing?
You rented this place, didn't you?
And it's in such a remote place.
What kind of life can you give her?
What kind of life can he give you?
He has no house and no car.
Is this the life you want to live?
Sir.
I have a job.
I can take good care of my family.
What can you take care of?
She could have had a better life!
Because of you,
she has to suffer with you!
Is this what you call taking care of her?
Dad, stop it.
I've already made up my mind.
No matter what the future holds,
I will be with him.
-You...
-Jin Baihui.
Just keep being stubborn.
The days of suffering
are yet to come!
Don't be sad.
Didn't we agree
to make your parents believe
we're really together?
I guess it's a success now.
I'm sorry
that you got scolded and wronged.
It's fine.
I'm thick-skinned.
It's okay.
We're just helping each other out.
Bros help each other out.
Thank you.
[Huacheng City Hejia Hospital]
[Hematology Department Ward]
You've been doing well
these past two days.
The nurses all praised you to me.
This is a reward for you.
Thank you, Dr. Shen.
Since I've been doing so well,
Dr. Shen,
could you take a photo with me?
The hospital has rules.
No taking photos together.
Just one.
I lost a bet with my besties.
They all took photos
with their math teachers,
and I'm the only one who didn't.
Absolutely no photos together.
But you can take a photo of me.
Just don't include
this equipment in the shot.
That works.
Dr. Shen, stand still.
Smile a little.
Strike a handsome pose.
Make a peace sign.
Three, two, one.
Cheese!
Is something on your mind today?
But you still look handsome.
I shouldn't have agreed to this.
Turn off the light and go to sleep.
This therapy is too new.
The risk is extremely high.
The current estimated survival rate
is only a little over ten percent.
To put it bluntly, this is a huge gamble.
Shui, are you asleep?
Wait a moment.
Come in.
[Huacheng City Hejia Hospital]
[Hematology Department Ward]
Shui.
I have to tell you something right now,
something very important
and serious.
After you hear it,
the choice is yours.
Why are you here?
I'm here to visit you.
Seriously...
I've been extremely busy lately.
Currently, our company
is increasingly expanding.
I have to split myself
in two to handle it.
Stop putting on airs.
If your business is expanding,
why don't you hire more people?
This is the excellent quality
of a good boss
who handles things personally.
Show-off.
Drink it while it's hot.
I have to say,
this coffee came right on time.
I was really too sleepy.
What good stuff is this?
Your favorite.
I can always count on you, Tang.
Let me take a call.
Don't dawdle. Just say it.
Speak.
No, how many times do I have to say it?
Stop trying to persuade me.
I think this issue
is not important right now.
Everything has its priorities.
You think your problem
is the most important now,
but it's exactly the opposite.
I think a technological upgrade
is the top priority.
Unbelievable.
What's wrong?
Why the big temper?
This company is full of crap.
I don't even know
why I hired these people.
Duan Qiyan, I don't mean to criticize you,
but can you be a little more patient?
You've had this bad habit since childhood.
There's a problem
with your communication style.
How can you negotiate anything like this?
No, do you even know
what I'm talking about
before you start scolding me?
I just don't get it.
I, Duan Qiyan,
am at least a boss to others.
Why, in your eyes, Tang Tingting,
am I capable
of nothing?
Am I that useless?
Duan Qiyan, why are you getting mad at me?
I shouldn't have bothered with your crap.
This late again?
What do you want to eat?
I'll make it for you.
Actually,
I'm not that hungry.
Then...
Just sit for a while?
♪ I'm like the gentle clouds in the sky ♪
I really want to try the strawberry crepes
♪ Looking forward
to the stop of the night breeze ♪
at that place you mentioned.
Then let's go there now.
Now?
♪ I'm wandering about carefully,
looking for the answer, so at a loss ♪
Yes.
Sit tight and hold on.
I'm going to speed up.
Don't worry. The crepes won't get away.
Let's go!
Go!
♪ Sometimes I wonder
if I should back down ♪
♪ Sudden alienation between us
is what scares me the most ♪
♪ How can two hearts beat as one
and truly feel each other? ♪
[Strawberry crepes sold out]
♪ The meteors fly past,
silencing thoughts ♪
See? The strawberry crepes got away.
We'll come back next time
and catch them.
It was my first time living with someone
other than Dad, Mom, and Zeqiu.
There was no awkwardness or discomfort,
only a natural connection
and happiness in every second.
This feeling is so wonderful.
Just like the Gaussian integral,
the calculation process
is beautiful and magical,
and the result is even more unexpected.
The only person
who can give me this feeling
is Jiang Yubai.